Since you have recognised that His Word is healing, deliverance, blessing,
the Lord will give me the grace - the Living Word in me will release you.
Those of you who have recognised that His Word is healing, deliverance, salvation, let me see your hand.
This is just what you need to recognise - that His Word is healing.
Once you have recognised that His Word is healing,
the Mighty God will let the Living Word in me to release you.
Thank you. Hallelujah.
Before I get to you...
Every contrary spirit around, please would you stand up!
Come on!
Stand up, come on!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up, come here!
Come here!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Take her there.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I am the spirit of darkness. I have destroyed her life.
There is no marriage - what marriage?
There is no affection.
There is no movement in her career.
From the time she was born.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I have destroyed him.
He can't move, he can't do anything.
Look here! Come on! Come here!
You said what? You will kill her?
I will kill her and kill the whole family in the house.
Ok. Tell her to go out down there.
I will kill her, I will stop at nothing.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
You over there - bring her out!
Come out!
Where you are going?
Stand up!
Stand up, come here!
Bring her here!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Stand up, come out!
Bring her out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Can I help you?
Come on!
Leave me!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Bring her out!
In the name of Jesus!
Come on, take her out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
I am the spiritual husband.
We are five.
Bring her out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
She can't bear children.
Stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I finished her.
I want her to die.
Come out!
Who are you?
I am a king.
King from where?
From the water.
What have you done to him?
I have destroyed him.
In what way?
He was in Nigeria. He went to Europe. I got him back.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
We destroyed his ministry.
Leave her!
Come on, stand up!
He went to Accra that he would do God's work.
How did you destroy him?
We put sickness in his body all the time.
He will always be in pain.
We put sickness in his body. He will always be in pain.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
There must always be problems.
How did you enter him?
Through food.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I destroyed her womb.
I destroyed her husband.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
He is a great man. He doesn't want to serve me.
Thank You, Jesus. I am healed!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I don't like her. I hate her.
Stand up!
I'm the idol.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
What is the meaning of this?
How did you destroy her? Her marriage?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Sacrifice.
She is my property.
I will kill her.
What career?
She says she is a business woman.
We shall see.
That business will collapse or she will die.
She is mine.
I am the family idol, 2000 years old.
I destroyed her marriage, I entered her husband.
I entered the husband. I destroyed her marriage. Now, she files for divorce.
She wants to withdraw it.
What is the meaning of this tatoo?
It has no meaning. Frustration.
How did you destroy the marriage?
I entered the husband through fornication.
Who are you in this body?
Spirit of destruction.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I am the spirit of seduction.
Who are you in this body?
I am a strong man.
How did you enter his body?
Through dream.
I cannot bend.
I cannot walk properly. Help me, Man of God.
Help me, Man of God.
For 3 years now. Man of God, help me.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Healed in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus, I am free.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I can bend now. Thank You, Jesus.
Who are you?
I have destroyed him.
How did you destroy him?
He is my husband.
Who are you?
I am his wife.
What have you done to his marriage?
I have destroyed everything.
How did you destroy his marriage?
No peace.
How did you enter him?
From the mother...
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
From her husband's place.
Who are you in this body? You have a name?
Stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Who are you?
She is mine.
What have you done to her?
How did you destroy her?
She can't! I finished her!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand right! Come on!
I will kill her!
I will destroy her in this pregnancy!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Spiritual husband.
She can never get peace!
I destroyed her career, I destroyed everything!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I destroyed everything! No money!
Who are you?
Idol.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
How did you enter this body?
Stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Healing in Jesus' Name
I destroyed everything.
Who are you in this body?
I'm a strong man.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Healed in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Thank You, Jesus, I am healed.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus. I can move now.
I can move now. Thank You, Jesus.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come on, stand up!
Leave her!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I want to destroy them!
They are struggling to survive!
They will not survive!
They are supposed to serve me!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Please, Man of God, help me. I cannot walk. I am having difficulty walking.
I am using a walking aid.
I have a lumbar corset on my waist.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Please, Man of God, help me. I am booked for two more surgeries on my back.
Help me, Man of God, please!
I had a surgery on my back. I'm booked for two more on my cervical and thoracic.
It is dead from my waist down; I don't have any feelings at all.
I have to wear a knee brace to help me walk, and a lumbar corset to help me sit up straight.
Man of God, help me.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Healing in Jesus' Name
I have no feelings from my waist down.
I have no feelings from my waist down. Everything is dead.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Help me, Jesus. Deliver me, please, God.
Free me, my Lord.
Stand up !
Healing in Jesus' Name
Walk!
Healed in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
I can walk now!
Are you ready to sit quietly? OK, let me continue, I want to get you there.
Healed in Jesus' Name
The feeling is coming. Thank You, Jesus. I can feel my knees.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
She is the owner. She is the house woman.
She speaks and the house quiets down.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
What have you done to her?
I have destroyed her.
How many are in this body?
Spirit of disappointment.
What have you done to her and to her family ?
I caused her mum sickness.
Stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I put a mask on her face.
Why did you do that? Why did you put a mask on her face?
How did you enter this body?
I entered her through dream.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up, come on!
In the name of Jesus, out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
I want his marriage.
I destroyed his wife.
We are the spirits.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Leave her!
Come out! Look here!
Let me go!
I tied her down.
I cause her disappointment.
She can never go forward in life. I hold her down.
Why did she come here?
What have you done to her?
I told her not to come here.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come on, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I destroyed her through her father's compound.
I don't want her to go to school, I don't want her to get married because she is very rich.
I am the forefather.
How did you enter her?
When she was little.
Stand up! Spirit of what?
Epilepsy, sir.
I command it out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Thank You, Jesus!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come on!
What have you done to her?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
What have you done to her marriage?
I destroyed her marriage!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
How did you enter her?
Through dreams.
Stand up!
It's a spirit. I separated her. I separated her not to marry.
Leave me alone!
The spirit of python.
What have you done to her?
I destroyed her marriage.
How did you destroy her marriage?
How?
I made her husband to run away from her!
What else have you done to her?
Sickness.
How did you enter her?
Her mother dedicated her to me.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come on, take her out!
Leave her!
My father has difficulty breathing. He has allergies.
He needs help. He can't walk without this machine.
Please, I am begging you.
Help us, Prophet.
Prophet, please.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
He has lung fibrosis. He needs help.
Please, help him.
He has got a machine, he has to walk with it all the time.
He has breathing problems.
Prophet, I need help. I have lung fibrosis. I cannot breathe.
I have problems. I can't do anything.
You came from where?
From the United States.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Can I help you in the name of Jesus?
Yes.
Okay.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Leave the place.
That is operation. He is gone now.
Can you see?
Healing in Jesus' Name
He is gone.
By the time he comes back, he will be well.
He is in the theatre where they are operating him.
Healing in Jesus' Name
He is gone.
Now, he is coming back. He is coming back.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Remove it.
Healed in Jesus' Name
Ok, walk!
Don't run.
Healed in Jesus' Name
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. Thank you.
Come here!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Thank you.